{
    "subject": "Rex_Harrison",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lilli_Palmer",
    "human_readable": "Rex Harrison is married to Lilli Palmer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881834387779236,
            "question": "Is Lilli Palmer married to Rex Harrison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9800218939781189,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Rex Harrison and Lilli Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.972140908241272,
            "question": "Were Rex Harrison and Lilli Palmer ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9116915464401245,
            "question": "Who is Rex Harrison married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8855758905410767,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Rex Harrison and Lilli Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8694719672203064,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Rex Harrison and Lilli Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8163589835166931,
            "question": "Who was Rex Harrison's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852801084518433,
            "question": "Name a famous actor who was married to Lilli Palmer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6874678134918213,
            "question": "What is the name of Rex Harrison's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5640520453453064,
            "question": "What is the name of Lilli Palmer's husband?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rex Harrison is married to Lilli Palmer.",
            "html": "yago_21926_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Rex Harrison's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_21926_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous actor who was married to Lilli Palmer.",
            "html": "yago_21926_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Rex Harrison's wife?",
            "html": "yago_21926_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21926_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the triple \"Rex Harrison is married to Lilli Palmer\".\n\nHere's my assessment:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21926/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt, it is mentioned that \"Lilli Palmer and Rex Harrison were married for 14 years.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21926/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt, it is stated that \"Actress Lilli Palmer (Rex Harrison\u2019s wife between 1943-1956)\".\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21926/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt, the same statement about Lilli Palmer being Rex Harrison's wife is repeated.\n\nGiven this information, it appears that the triple \"Rex Harrison is married to Lilli Palmer\" is supported by the context documents. Therefore:\n\n`{ 'output': 'yes' }`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Lilli Palmer and Rex Harrison, confirming that they were indeed married."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}